# **Curriculum Vitae**

#### **Lewis Warner**

86 Wincheap, Canterbury, Kent, CT1 3RS

<u>Email: lwarner103@live.com</u> <u>Tel:</u> 07508265502

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lewis-warner-b90ab820a/

## **PERSONAL PROFILE**

After several years of working in the Transport industry, at the age of 26 years old, I began my educational journey towards becoming a secondary school teacher of Computing. I am passionate about the use of computers in education and truly believe my enthusiasm and knowledge and will enable me to be inspirational. I am somebody who strives to be adaptable, hardworking, a confident communicator and listener with a positive and compassionate attitude towards others.

Research Methods (tbc)
Database Enhancement

Helping Users and the ITL

**Network and Operating** 

E-Business Systems (tbc)

Group Project (tbc)

Framework (tbc)

Systems (tbc)

#### **EDUCATION**

# 2020-23 Canterbury Christ Church University

**BSc (Hons):** Computing (Expected overall grade: 1<sup>st</sup> or 2:1)

1st Year (grade tbc)2nd Year (grade tbc)Deployment TechnologiesUsing Technology for businessfor Computing (1st)Improvement (tbc)

Fundamentals of Computer Systems (1st)

Introduction to C# (1st)
Software Lifecycle Group
Development Project (tbc)
Ethics, Professionalism and

Employability in

Computing (tbc)

Application Development in C# (tbc)

2<sup>nd</sup> Year (grade tbc) 3<sup>rd</sup> Year (tbc)

Individual Study – Part A (tbc)

Cybersecurity (tbc)

Individual Study – Part B (tbc) Human Computer Interaction (tbc) Current Issues in Computing (tbc) Advanced Networking (tbc)

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

October 2018 - Present - F.W. Mansfield, Canterbury, Kent.

**Position:** HGV Class 1 Driver

Transportation of fruit/farm equipment between sites within the business.

April 2016 – October 2018 - Lenham Storage, Maidstone, Kent.

Position: HGV Class 2 & HGV Class 1 Driver

Multi-drop delivery/collection of palletised goods to stores/distribution hubs around the UK

January 2016 – April 2016 - Young Brothers Transport, Faversham, Kent.

Position: HGV Class 2 Driver

Local multi-drop delivery/collection of palletised goods to homes/businesses.

May 2015 - December 2015 - Lenham Storage, Maidstone, Kent.

**Position:** HGV Class 2 Driver

Multi drop delivery/collection of palletised goods to supermarket stores

August 2014 - May 2015 - Eclipse Recovery Services, Canterbury, Kent.

Position: HGV Class 2 Driver

Recovery/transportation of accident damaged/broken vehicles.

**2012 – August 2014 - Domino's Pizza, Kent.** 

**Position:** Assistant Manager

Responsible for managing store in absence of Store Manager. Rotas, stock control, cleaning, customer service, ensuring targets are met.

## 2010-2012 - Domino's Pizza, Kent.

**Position:** Customer Services Representative / Shift Manager

Serving customers, running shifts in absence of Assistant or Store Manager

## **SECONDARY EDUCATION**

## 2019 - 2020 - The Open University

Access Module (Y033) – Science, Technology and Maths (Distinction)

## **2009-2010** - The Maplesden Noakes School, Maidstone, Kent.

GCSE's - English (B), Maths (C), Science (B), ICT (A), English Literature (B), D&T:

Resistant Materials (B),

French (B), Music (C), Business & Communication Systems (B), Statistics (C), Religious Studies (D),

Edexcel - Level 2 Certificate in Digital Applications (Pass)

## **2008** – The Astor of Hever Community School, Maidstone, Kent.

**GCSE** - Statistics (C)

**OCR** - Level 1 Certificate in Business Language Competence (French)

#### **OVERVIEW OF SKILLS**

<u>Customer Service/Communication</u>: Throughout my career both in retail and lorry driving, I have had to interact with both customers, off-site and office staff. This has enabled me to gain a high level of communication skills and experience dealing with people from different environments. This has developed my problem solving and evaluation skills and ability to reflect on situations that arise.

<u>Leadership Skills:</u> My time as a manager at Domino's has enabled me to develop my skills and ability to manage groups of people in a high-pressured environment. My time at University has also renewed my recognition of the importance of teamwork and has given me the chance to improve and demonstrate my leadership skills on various group projects.

<u>Technical Skills:</u> I have a very good knowledge of basic ICT literacy skills and have begun to advance my computing skills in areas such as coding, testing, database, software, high/low level requirements.

## **INTERESTS**

I have a keen interest in music and am currently taking Piano Lessons. I have also recently started taking an interest in health/fitness.

# **REFERENCES**

**Dr Anne Nortcliffe – Canterbury Christ Church University,** Canterbury, Kent.

**<u>Position:</u>** Founding Head of School of Engineering, Technology and Design

Email: anne.nortcliffe@canterbury.ac.uk Tel: 01227 921862

Nathan Jordan - F. W. Mansfield & Son, Nickle Farm, A28 Chartham, Canterbury, Kent.

**Position:** Transport/Site Manager

Email: jordann@mansfields.net Tel: 01227 731441